<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CircuitTraining</string>

    <integer name="num_images">32</integer>
    <integer name="num_columns">8</integer>
    <string name="wire_mode_label">*Wire*\nMode</string>
    <string name="addWireButton">Add Wire</string>
    <string name="selectGateButton">Select Gate</string>
    <string name="undoButton">Undo</string>
    <string name="splash_screen_title"> Circuit\nTraining</string>
    <string name="splash_screen_hint_text">Click to Begin</string>
    <string name="and_gate">
        The AND gate is so named because it acts in the same way as the logical "and" operator. The output is "true" when both inputs are "true." Otherwise, the output is "false."
    </string>
    <string name="nand_gate">
        The NAND gate operates as an AND gate followed by a NOT gate. It acts in the manner of the logical operation "and" followed by negation. The output is "false" if both inputs are "true." Otherwise, the output is "true."
    </string>
    <string name="nor_gate">
        The NOR gate is a combination OR gate followed by a NOT gate. Its output is "true" if both inputs are "false." Otherwise, the output is "false."
    </string>
    <string name="not_gate">
        A NOT gate requires a single connection. It will only output if this connection is switched off, and will not output if the connection is switched on.
    </string>
    <string name="or_gate">
        The OR gate gets its name from the fact that it behaves after the fashion of the logical inclusive "or." The output is "true" if either or both of the inputs are "true." If both inputs are "false," then the output is "false."
    </string>
    <string name="xnor_gate">
        The XNOR (exclusive-NOR) gate is a combination XOR gate followed by a NOT gate. Its output is "true" if the inputs are the same, and "false" if the inputs are different.    </string>
    <string name="xor_gate">
        The XOR ( exclusive-OR ) gate acts in the same way as the logical "either/or." The output is "true" if either, but not both, of the inputs are "true."
    </string>
    <string-array name="Instruction_manual_title">
        <item>
            Welcome to Circuit Training
        </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item>
            Switches
        </item>
        <item>
            Bulbs
        </item>
        <item>
            Logic Gates
        </item>
        <item>
            Wires
        </item>
        <item>
            Completing the Circuit
        </item>
        <item> </item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="instruction_manual">
        <item>
            This is a application to teach you about logic gates.\n
            Logic gates are extremely useful, and are the building blocks for all digital circuits.\n
            The microchips that we use in our computers contain logic gates!
        </item>
        <item>
            You will be set a series of challenges to complete a problem using logic gates.
            Each game board begins with 2 basic elements: Switches and Light Bulbs.
        </item>

        <item>
            Switches can be switched on and off.When they are switched on they will emit a positive charge -
            like a light switch!\n
            Like ordinary light bulbs, the bulbs will switch on when they get a current.
        </item>
        <item>
            To add a logic gate, press the \"Select Gate\" button.\n
            This will show you the 7 logic gates you can use in your circuit\n
            If you are new to logic gates or unsure what the gates do,
            click the \"More Info\" button to find out more about the gate.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            To add a wire to the circuit, click the \"Add Wire\" button to enter "Add Wire" mode.\n
            To begin adding a wire, press and hold the place you wish the wire to start.\n
            To end the wire, press and hold the component you wish to connect the wire to.\n
            It is worth noting that wires cannot start and end in the same place.\n
            Wire can also not end on a power switch ,or begin from a bulb.
        </item>
        <item>
            To complete the puzzle you must use logic gates and wires to connect the
            switches and the bulbs together.\n
            The circuits must also be complete. To do this all power switches must be part of
            the circuit and all logic gates must also be connected fully.\n
            This means that they must have 2 inputs (apart from NOT gates which only have 1 input)
            and they must also have an output.
        </item>
        <item>
            If you make a mistake you can restart the circuit by
            shaking your device, or pressing the \"Undo\" button.
            So ....are you ready to start?
        </item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="questions">
        <item>When all 3 switches are on both bulbs are on</item>
        <item>When all 3 switches are on both bulbs are off</item>
        <item>When all switches are off all bulbs lit</item>
        <item>When switch a and b are lit all bulbs are off</item>
        <item>When all switches are off only the top bulb is on</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
